1mgayush.com 2016-04-04

# Privacy Policy & Terms - Homeobuy

1MG Technologies Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as the company) committed to safeguard your privacy online. However, to be an informed and aware customer you are requested to read the Privacy Policy carefully.

**We may collect following personal information about you:** ****

\- Name including first and last name

\- Email address

\- Mobile phone number and contact details

\- Age, Date of birth

\- Area ZIP/Postal code

\- Credit card or Debit card numbers

\- Other information as required by the registration processes

We will not use your personal and financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction and process your orders.

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties.

We will endeavour to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal and financial information. However, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized or fraudulent acts of third parties.

Cookie technology will only be used to track some non-personal information such as IP address, type of browser, operating system and domain names etc. to improve our site and to facilitate transactions. 

When you place orders it is through a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input including your credit card number, before it is sent to us. This makes it unreadable as it travels across the Internet.

_We reserve the right to change or update above policy at any time by placing a notice on the website. Such changes or updated shall be effective immediately upon posting to the website._
